whooshkaa.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Whooshkaa

###### 1\. Introduction

To provide you with the Whooshkaa service (the “Service”), we, Whooshkaa Pty Ltd, www.whooshkaa.com, (“Whooshkaa”, “we”, “us”, “our”), need to collect some information about you. This Privacy Policy is where we describe the information we collect, what we do with it, and how you can manage and control the use of your information. We also describe what a cookie is and how we use them. If you don‘t agree with these terms, then please do not use the Service.

* * *

###### 2\. The information we collect

When you sign up for the Service, we may collect information we ask you for, like your name, password, e-mail, date of birth, gender and location. We will also collect information you voluntarily add to your profile. If you connect to the Service using your Facebook credentials, you authorize us to collect your authentication information, such as your username, encrypted access credentials, and such other information that may be available through your Facebook account.

We also automatically collect certain information when the Service is used, including: (i) your interactions with the Service, including which podcasts you listen to; (ii) user content you contribute to the Service; (iii) technical data, which may include your IP address, network, language, operating system and Whooshkaa application version; and (iv) location information.

* * *

###### 3\. How we use the information we collect

We may use the information we collect, including your personal information, to: improve your experience with the Service, for example by providing customized or localized content and/or advertising;

  1. ensure the correct functioning and running of the Service;
  2. develop new products and services;
  3. analyze your use of the Service, including your interaction with the application or website, advertising, third party services that are made available, linked to or offered through the Service; 
  4. communicate with you for Service-related purposes, including promotional e-mails or messages or messages regarding updates to any terms and conditions, or the Service; 
  5. to protect the rights and security of Whooshkaa, its users or any other person; and
  6. as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.

* * *

###### 4\. How we share the information we collect

We may share the information we collect, including your personal information, as follows:

  1. We are building an interactive audio on demand Service that offers many ways to find, enjoy, and share content with others. We encourage our users to use the social functions of the Service, for example to explore who else is using the Service, and therefore parts of your Whooshkaa information may be publicly available to others by default, such as your name, profile picture, your friends on the Service and your activity. 
  2. Whooshkaa enables you to share a particular item of content, for example part of a podcast, to third party services or other Whooshkaa users by using the Service’s share functionality. Please note that sharing of such content on a third party service (for example Facebook or Twitter) may be posted as activity on the Service and on said third party service. To share an individual item of content to a third party service, you’ll be prompted to enter your access credentials for that third party service. Whooshkaa may store your username and access token or similar credentials obtained from the third party service, so that you are able to share particular items of content, on that third party service, on an individual basis, without entering your access credentials again. You understand and agree that Facebook’s, Twitter’s or other third parties’ use of information they collect from you is governed by their privacy policies, and Whooshkaa’s use of such information is governed by this Privacy Policy. 

We may from time to time share your information within the Whooshkaa group as well as certain trusted business partners and third party service providers to enable them to perform functions and process user data on our behalf. Such processing of user data will always be subject to security and confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

Finally, we may also share your information to third parties for the following purposes:

  * to allow a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets;
  * to respond to legal process, if we believe in good faith that it is necessary to do so;
  * to comply with requirements of mandatory applicable law;
  * to protect the safety of any person;
  * to protect the rights and property of Whooshkaa, any user or a third party; and to address fraud, security or technical issues;
